Guide to the George Henry Nettleton Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Additional material, 1917-1964, undated; Accession 2003-M-038
  - Subject files (Box 1)
    - Exams for English drama classes, 1922, undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Lecture notes, postcard, negative, 1925-1939, undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Pierson College Master's House guest book, 1949 September-1953 May (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Unidentified notes, undated (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Writings
    - Miles, Anna Nettleton [title page missing], 1944 December (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Nettleton, Mary Treat (Mrs. George), notes, school compositions, stories, 1881, 1882, undated (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Photographs [some in postcard form]
    - Nettleton, George [individual and group], [1891], 1892, 1935, undated (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - American University of Paris, undated (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Buildings, historical sites, undated (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Unidentified, mostly family, 1951, undated (Box 2, Folder 37)